It's been a while, Tanjiro. Long time no see. Feel free to make yourself at home.
It's good to see you too. I'm glad to see you're doing well.
And you too, Tanjiro. At 3 o'clock, I'm going to brew some black tea that'll make us pancakes with lots and lots of butter, okay?
Butter? Pancakes? I barely know what black tea is.
We'll have sweets, bread, and pancakes!
There you go! Enjoy!
Help yourself and dig in!
How exactly do I eat something like this?
Here, I'll show you.
Ready, Tanjiro? Open wide!
Uh, sure!
Well, what do you think, Tanjiro?
It's so tasty, it's to die for!
It really is delicious, isn't it?
It is!
Oh, and Tanjiro!
When you're done, can you change into this?
Don't you believe me?
Yeah.
Oh
Ready
All right
Try to stay in sync everybody
Extend those arms more
Jump as far as you can
Good
Now twirl all the way around
It's important that you stay flexible
It'll help make all your movements more snappy
So limber up everyone
And give me a big stretch
No that's not how I taught you
I'll show you how it's done
Let's switch
Here we go
Take it there
This isn't limbering up
It's torture
All right
Come on it's your turn now Tanjiro
What?
Are you ready?
Here we go
Flexibility is
Help
Hello Tanjiro Kamado
I've been waiting for you here for some time
I can't wait to train
Shut up
Or I'll kill you
Kanroji told me all about you in a letter
And judging by what she said
It sounds like it was awfully fun training under her
Huh?
I bet you had all sorts of fun didn't you?
I've got a letter for you from Lady Kanroji
Dear Mr. Igaro
How are you?
After training today
I sat down and had black tea with Tanjiro
Tanjiro's so cute
Whenever he eats or drinks something sweet
He looks like he died and went to heaven
Isn't that adorable?
Kamado
No
I won't go easy on you like Kanroji did
Understand
It's day one and he already hates me with a burning passion
This is the training I have in store for you
I'm going to have you strike targets I've placed
While avoiding these whiny obstacles
To refine your swordsmanship skills
Okay
But why does this feel more like
An execution ground
So the people who are tied up in here
Did they commit a crime or something?
I suppose you could say that
The crime of weakness
The crime of incompetence
The crime of wasting my time
The crime of annoying me
They're lucky to be alive
Oh no
What am I gonna do?
You'll be using this
I'm only showing you once
So pay attention
And that's it
To be so accurate
While navigating the space
Between all the swordsmen
At such speed
Let's see you do it
Please don't hit me
Please don't hit us
Get on with it already
Right
What an absolute joke
You called that sad display training
I'll take you on myself then
Now strike me
Strike you?
Right
Please don't hit me
You hesitated
My hands are totally tied
Again
Cramped space or not
I have to land a strike
You're slow
It's no good
I'm too worried about hitting
One of the other swordsmen
Stand up
Start over from the beginning
And so the most terrifying training began
I may be using a wooden sword
But it could still cause serious injury
I have to maneuver between these poor swordsmen
While dodging Mr. Iguro's attacks
This is dangerous
Especially since his sword strikes
Twist and turn in such an abnormal way
You're slow
We're both wielding the same kind of sword
So how can his bend like that?
His strikes are able to weave and slither
Their way past obstacles
Just like a serpent
What's worse
I can't unhear them
The muffled cries for help
From my fellow trainees
As I swing past them
Please, please, please, please, please
They're saying please don't hit me
I can hear every plea
And each one pierces my soul
Don't hesitate
You piece of trash
I've never felt tension like this
My hands couldn't stop shaking
If I don't swing my sword with pinpoint accuracy
Someone could really get hurt
Sorry
Hey, Kamado
How are you able to keep going
After training so hard with the Hashira?
Because if I miss once
I could injure one of you
Come on, you guys
Let's join it
Yeah, why not?
Oh, no
This will make our cut sting, won't it?
How bad could it be?
All right
Here it goes
You sure?
We'll go together
Ready, set
That really stings
Still slow
If you're going to strike at that speed
This drill is pointless
Yes, sir
Now you're lunging even slower
Get a grip
It stings
You're slow
You're too slow
Ouch
It stings
What's wrong?
Have you given up, slowpoke?
I've got to focus solely on battling Mr. Igoro
In a real fight
If your sword gets caught on something
It's fatal
Avoid all the obstacles
And swing your sword
It's as simple as that
My strikes are becoming more accurate
I'm getting the hang of it
I can evade Mr. Igoro's attacks
And because of my training
Land my own
Once you land a strike
And slash one of Mr. Igoro's Hauri sleeves
They say that you're finished with his training
Thank you for your hard work
Leave my sight
Before I change my mind and kill you
And stop getting chummy with Konroji, brat
It makes me sad to know that he hated me from start to finish
What'd I do?
Let's see
Mr. Shinazugawa's dojo is this way
Birdbrain!
You're supposed to turn right here!
How dumb can you be?
Oh, we turned right there, huh?
Whoa!
Zenitsu!
I'm begging you, please help me escape!
Tanju, Tanju, you gotta help me!
Help you escape from what?
I'm not even able to stay upright anymore!
It took me forever just to get this far away!
I had to crawl along the walls!
Masking my presence like a lizard!
My life is on the line!
Please help me!
Make up your mind!
Either come back to training
Or be killed where you stand!
Please spare my pathetic life!
Please calm down!
Shut up!
Carry him
Uh, yes, sir!
Sorry, Zenitsu
We'll get through this together
Long time no see!
I'll be training under you starting today!
I can hardly wait!
Don't get too cocky, kid
I haven't deemed you worthy of my respect, you got that?
That doesn't bother me at all!
See, I actually don't respect you either!
You stabbed Nezuko!
You've got some nerve
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Mr. Shinazugawa's drills were so harsh, I could understand why Zenitsu ended up like that
It was a simple striking drill in which we all took turns assaulting Mr. Shinazugawa
We had no choice but to keep going
Until we spewed vomit or passed out
To make matters worse, there were no breaks
Even Mr. Igorou let us rest a little bit
Hmm
When Zenitsu came too, he berated me as if he were avenging his parents' death
I hate you, you jerk!
Ow, ow, I'm sorry!
Mr. Shinazugawa was especially harsh on me
If I had let my guard down for even a second, I would have ended up right back in treatment
I can't start my training here like this
Battered, bruised, and covered in my own vomit
It's soul-crushing
Big bro, wait up!
Kenya's here?
There's something I want to tell you
Learn some boundaries
And I don't recall having a younger brother
If you don't give me some space, I'll eviscerate you
That's not like the sibling fights we had
Do you surrender?
Cut it out, big brother!
Stop talking to me like we're close or something, you freak
Judging by the looks of you, you're useless
And if you don't have any skills to show
Then quit the Demon Slayer core
You can't even use breathing techniques, right?
And you're not a real swordsman
I can't, but
Hey, hold on before you go
I've been wanting to apologize to you all this time
That's it, Kenya
Don't give up
I really couldn't care less
Now get lost
But brother
I've even eaten demons
Just to be able to fight
You what?
What did you just say?
You bastard
Demons?
You've eaten demons
He's gone
Genya
How many more days is this torture gonna last, huh?
He's back
He's back, he's back, he's back
Quick, lie down and pretend you passed out
It's the only way we'll be spared
Is that Tanjiro?
What the?
You'll be killed, Tanjiro
What are you doing destroying the building like that?
Please, calm down
Hold on
What's that twisted, ominous sound that's coming from inside?
The old guy's on a rampage
We're getting clobbered during and after training
What do you think you're doing?
You could have killed him
If I wanted him dead, he would be
We're not allowed to kill trainees
But I have something else planned
I'm going to break him beyond recovery
I tell you what
If he quits the Demon Slayer Corps right here and now
I'll let him go
How dare you?
There's no way you have that kind of authority
You can't force him to quit
And you just said yourself that you had no brother
So you have no say in what choices Genya makes
Whether he has skills or not
He's decided to risk his life fighting demons
If you're not his brother
Then I'm not letting you stand in his way
Without Genya, that upper rank would have beaten us
So I won't let you hurt him
Genya's my friend
Is that right?
Then I'll just go ahead and break you beyond recovery first
Here he comes
Focus
Tanjiro
Damn brat
He stopped my fist
He landed a blow
Zenitsu
Get Genya out of here quickly
Are you stupid or something?
Don't call me by my name in front of him
There's gotta be a better way to signal to me
Tanjiro
He only grazed me but that kick ripped my ear
You've really got some nerve taking me on like this
If you've got a death wish
I'd love to help you out with that
Stop it brother
You got nothing to do with this
Let's go
Who are you?
Let go of me
The enemy won't be able to focus on us all at once if we split up
So that guy's your big brother?
He's a total lunatic
I feel bad you had to
Don't you dare insult my older brother
I'm on your side you idiot
Just die already
From that point on it was a frenzy of chaos and turmoil
The brawl nearly lasted until dusk
What were you thinking back there you idiot?
I received a formal reprimand from the higher ups
My training under the wind Hashira was suspended
And I was banned from going near him again
In the end
I wasn't able to bring the Shinazugawa brothers together as I'd hoped
Not only did I get us kicked out of his training sessions
But my mark still isn't any clearer
And I feel like I haven't grown at all from my training
You definitely have
After all you took on the old wind guy right?
That's incredible
You really think so?
Just how deep in the mountains is the Stonehengeur's house?
Is he a hermit?
I think it's just a bit farther
What?
Is something wrong?
I hear something up ahead
This way
It's a waterfall
Hey look
Thus have I heard in the presence of the Buddha
If you are able to extinguish your heart and mind
Even fire becomes tolerable
Welcome boys
To my training ground
Our Luna is Heights
This made us look
Once again
We're here
Listen
By one
Where
We're here
Full
Let's
I'll hit you later.
Thank you.
Today, we're talking about Mr. Iguro.
You're still here?
You better not be making a pass at Kanroji.
It's not like that!
And I'm telling a Taisho era secret!
Then get it over with.
All right, here's a Taisho era secret.
The name of the snake Mr. Iguro has is Kaburamaru.
He says that his left and right eyes have been different colors since birth.
If that's everything, then get out of here and stay away from Kanroji.
But we're friends.
So you are planning on seeing her.
Whoa!
Episode 6, the strongest of the Demon Slayer Corps!